모니카, 최고의 추수감사절
저녁이었어, 너무 맛있다
Monica, that was the best
Thanksgiving dinner ever.
It was so good.
I think you killed us.
우리 다 죽었다
이젠 더 못 먹겠어
I couldn't possibly eat another bite.
I need something sweet.
달짝지근한 건 없나?
Does anyone want to watch TV?
우리 TV나 볼까?
그래, 좋아
Monica, your remote doesn't work.
너희 리모콘 안 된다
들어서 눌러야지
You have to lift it and point.
Oh, forget it.
그만두자
Let's play that game where everyone
says one thing they're thankful for.
자기가 감사를 느끼는 거
한 가지씩 말하기로 하자
나, 이 아름다운 가을에
감사하고 싶어
I am thankful for this
beautiful fall we've been having.
그거 멋지다
Very nice.
전에 버스정류장에 있었는데
The other day,
I was at the bus stop...
가을의 산들바람이 불어와선
어떤 여자 치마를 뒤집더라고
...and this lovely fall breeze came
and blew this chick's skirt up.
Which reminds me,
I'm also thankful for thongs.
그러고 보니
실 팬티도 고맙구나
The One with the Thanksgiving Flashbacks
그건 단순히 팬티가 아니라
말 그대로 공학의 극치야
It's not so much an underpant
as a feat of engineering.
그렇게 적은 재료로
뭘 만들어내는지 보라고
It's amazing...
...how much they can do
with so little material.
사람 감질나게 하잖아
있는 걸까, 없는 걸까...
And they play with your mind.
Is it there? Is it not there?
Are you aware that
you're still talking?
너 지금 정신 있냐?
Is anyone thankful for anything else
besides a thong?
실 팬티 말고
감사할 거 없어?
I don't know. Am I more thankful
for my divorce or my eviction?
어떤 걸 골라야 할까
이혼이냐, 쫓겨난 거냐
And I didn't think you'd be able
to come up with anything.
넌 아무 것도 없을 줄 알았어
I'm sorry. This is
the worst Thanksgiving ever.
미안하다, 나로선
최악의 추수감사절이야
아니, 그 방면이라면
날 못 따라오지
I am the king of bad Thanksgivings.
You can't swoop in with your bad
marriage and take that away from me.
실패한 결혼얘기도
내 상대가 안 돼
또 너희 부모님 이혼한
얘기하려는 건 아니겠지?
You're not going to tell about your
parents' divorce again, are you?
- 맙소사, 안 돼
- 참아라
왜들 이래, 난 듣고 싶어
Come on! I want to hear it.
챈들러 헛소리가 빠지면
추수감사절도 아니지
It wouldn't be Thanksgiving
without Chandler bumming us out.
It's a tradition, like the parade.
퍼레이드 같은 전통이야
If the parade decided it was gay
and abandoned its family.
그게 가족을 버리고
집을 나간 게이라면
1978년 추수감사절
얘야, 챈들러
Now, Chandler, dear...
...just because
we're getting a divorce...
엄마아빠가 이혼한다고
널 사랑하지 않는 건 아냐
...doesn't mean we don't love you.
아빠는 엄마보다 하인이랑
자고 싶다는 뜻이란다
It just means...
...he would rather sleep
with the houseboy than with me.
More turkey, Mr. Chandler?
칠면조 더 드실래요
챈들러 도련님?
너 그 얘기할 때마다
하인 억양이 점점 세진다
Every time you tell that story,
that guy's accent gets thicker and thicker.
So are he and your dad still together?
아직 같이 사시니?
아니, 집 장만하시고
그 하인이 또 하인을 들였어
No. After they got their own place,
the houseboy got his own houseboy.
Should have heard his accent.
그 억양도 들어봐야 하는데
You're right, yours is worse.
You're the king of bad Thanksgivings.
그래, 끔찍하다
넌 불행한 추수감사절의 왕이야
I've got one that's worse.
글쎄, 난 더 심했는데
이거보다 더 심해?
'챈들러, 도련님?'
Really? Worse than,
"More turkey, Mr. Chandler?"
Did the little rich boy
have a problem with the butler?
집사한테 불만 있는 부잣집
도련님? 그래, 내 게 더 심해
Yes, mine's worse!
1862년 추수감사절
More bandages!
붕대 더! 붕대 더!
Please, can I get
some more bandages in here?
붕대 더 가져와요!
This man is
이 병사가...
잘한다
전생에서 말고
In this life, Phoebe.
Oh, this life. Oh, okay.
전생은 안 돼?
그럼 챈들러가 이겼다
No, Chandler's is worse.
It must be cool
remembering stuff like that.
그런 게 생각나면 좋겠다
난 전생의 기억이 없어
I don't have any past-life memories.
Of course, you don't, sweetie.
You're brand-new.
당연하지
넌 신제품이니까
I know Monica's worst Thanksgiving.
모니카의 추수감사절도 있지
Let's not tell this story.
그 얘기는 하지 말자
- 뭔데 그래?
- 해봐
아니, 내가 알아
I know!
It's the one where Joey got
Monica's turkey stuck on his head.
한번은 조이가 모니카의
칠면조에 머리를 박았어
- 뭐?
- 뭐야?
Joey got a turkey stuck on his head?
조이가 칠면조에 머리를 박았어?
그런 거 아냐
It's not like it sounds.
정확히 그런 거 맞아
It's exactly like it sounds.
1992년 추수감사절
여보세요?
여보세요
피비?
조이, 무슨 일이야?
What's going on?
Oh, my God!
엄마야!
I know!
그래, 박혔어!
It's stuck!
밑에 계단이야
어쩌다 그랬어?
Step.
How did it get on?
I put it on to scare Chandler.
챈들러 겁주려고 뒤집어썼지
Oh, my God! Monica's going to
totally freak out!
이걸 어째, 모니카가
알면 난리 날 텐데
Help me get it off!
그럼 어서 벗겨 줘
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
게다가 여기 냄새도 지독하다
당연하지, 죽은 동물
엉덩이 속인데
Of course it smells bad.
You have your head up a dead animal's ass.
오! 모니카다
- 왔어?
- 그래
칠면조는...
엄마야! 못살아!
Did you get the turkey?
Oh, my God!
Who is that?
누구야?
It's Joey.
조이란다
뭐 하는 거야?
그게 재미있어?
Is this supposed to be funny?
재미가 아니라
겁주려는 거래
It's not supposed to be funny.
It's supposed to be scary.
당장 빼
Get that off now!
I can't. It's stuck!
안 돼, 걸렸어
부모님 집에 온 손님들한테
네 머리를 대접하라는 거야?
It has to feed 20 people. They're
not going to eat it off your head!
Hold on.
잠깐, 우리 생각 좀 해보자
Let's just all think.
I got it!
- 이러면 되겠다, 피비
- 응?
You pull.
넌 당겨, 난 최대한
다리를 벌릴 테니까
I'll spread the legs
as wide as I can.
- 조이, 분위기 파악 좀 해!
- 그래, 알았어
Now is not the time.
좋아, 셋을 셀게
Count to three. One...
하나, 둘, 셋!
...two...
...three!
뜨아아아아!
It worked!
I scared you! I knew it!
거봐, 놀랐잖아
I'm here, big guy.
나 여기 있다
그래, 거기
Yeah, you are!
놀랐지롱
I scared you!
You did look like an idiot.
너 정말 바보 같더라
I wasn't the only one
who looked like an idiot.
나만 바보 같은 게 아냐
Remember when Ross tried to say
"butternut squash"...
로스는 '버터 넛 스쿼시'를
말하려다가...
'스쿼터 넛 버시'라고 했어
...and it came out,
"squatternut bosh"?
Yeah, that's the same.
똑같은 거야
- 그게 내 최악의 추수감사절이야
- 잠깐
That's it.
That's my worst Thanksgiving.
That can't be the one Rachel meant.
레이첼이 말한 건 그게 아냐
그런 일 있었는지도 모르는데
She didn't even know that happened.
- 맞아
- 그럼 뭐야?
So, what's yours?
I really don't want
to tell this story.
그건 진짜 말하기 싫어
서로 고통을 털어놓고 기분
잡치는 게 추수감사절이잖아
Reliving pain and getting depressed
is what Thanksgiving's all about.
For me, anyway.
어쨌든 난 그래
인디언들도 물론 그렇겠지
And, of course, the lndians.
다른 사람은 몰라도
넌 그러면 안 되지
Of all people, you do not want me
to tell this story.
What is that supposed to mean?
그건 무슨 뜻인데?
- 1987년 추수감사절
- 모니카, 레이첼 왔다
-Monica, I think Rachel's here!
-I'll get it!
제가 열게요
Happy Thanksgiving!
즐거운 추수감사절 맞아
Not for me.
난 아냐, 칩이랑 깨졌어
Chip and I broke up.
Why?
왜, 어쩌다 그랬어?
What happened?
엄마아빠 여행 중이라
칩이 집에 온 거 알지?
My parents are out of town,
and Chip was going to come over.
그래서 넌...
꽃을 준 댔잖아
And you were going to give him...
...your "flower."
Monica, can you just call it sex?
그냥 섹스라고 해
나 정말 소름끼친다
It really creeps me out
when you call it that.
And by the way...
어쨌든 말이 났으니 말인데
그 물건 정말 참을성 없더라
...while we're at it, a guy's thing
is not called his "tenderness."
진짜야
Believe me.
안녕, 레이첼
Happy Thanksgiving.
- 행복하세요
- 너도
저 왔어요
이런...
Everyone...
여러분, 이쪽은 챈들러예요
...this is Chandler.
My roommate...
제 룸메이트이자
우리 밴드의 리드싱어죠
...and lead singer of our band.
오빠...
This is Monica.
얘는 모니카
로스 오빠 동생이에요
I'm Ross' little sister.
그렇군요
I'm so glad you could come.
잘 왔어요, 음식은 많으니
맘껏 들고 가요
We've got plenty of food,
so I hope you're hungry.
얘는 추수감사절 싫어해서
아무 것도 안 먹을 거예요
Chandler hates Thanksgiving
and doesn't eat any Thanksgiving food.
I'm so glad you brought him here.
그럼 잘 데려왔구나
챈들러
I can make you some
macaroni and cheese for dinner.
괜찮으면 마카로니치즈
만들어줄게요
순례자들이 안 먹은 거라면 뭐
As long as the Pilgrims
didn't eat it.
Damn it!
젠장
저기, 레이첼
집안 분위기가
좀 허전하지 않아?
Does it feel weird around here now?
You know, since
I've been away at college?
내가 대학기숙사로 떠나서
Not really.
- 별로 안 그런데
- 잘됐다
That's cool.
근데...
So that's Rachel, the girl you've been
writing all those songs about?
쟤가 노래에 등장하는
그 레이첼인가?
그래
Might want to rethink the lyrics to
"She Feels Weird Since I've Been Gone."
내가 떠난 후 허전한 걸로
가사를 다시 생각해볼게
I cannot believe Chip dumped me
for that slut Nancy Branson!
그 걸레 같은 낸시 브랜슨
때문에 날 버릴 수 있어?
I am never going out with him again.
I don't care how much he begs.
다시는 안 만나줄 거야
무릎 꿇고 빌어도
낸시 브랜슨을 만나는데
너한테 왜 빌겠니?
His begging days are over, now
that he's with Nancy Branson.
I've just had it
with high-school boys.
고등학교 애들은 이제 지겹다
They're just silly.
머저리들이야
They're just silly, stupid boys.
하여간 멍청한 녀석들
I'll start dating men.
진짜 남자를 만날래
I'm sorry, Judy.
죄송합니다, 어머님
두 분께서 찾는 그릇이 없군요
I couldn't find that bowl
you and Jack were looking for.
Call them Mom and Dad, you loser.
엄마 아빠라고 해, 바보야
이게 걍...
챈들러
Did you like
the macaroni and cheese?
마카로니치즈 맛있어?
It was great.
You should be a chef.
훌륭하네
요리사 해도 되겠다
그래
Guess what.
신난다
All this stuff about Nancy
being a slut was all a rumor.
낸시 브랜슨 얘기는
다 헛소문이었어
칩이 걔 차버리고
오늘밤 우리 집에 온대
Chip dumped her, and he wants
to come over to my house!
정말 잘됐다
-That is so great!
-I know.
Oh, gosh. Listen,
if you and Chip do it tonight...
들어봐, 오늘밤에
둘이 하고 나서
꼭 얘기해 줘, 몽땅
...promise me
you'll tell me everything.
Totally. It's not that big a deal.
We already kind of did it once.
당연하지, 별거 아냐
벌써 한 번 했는데 뭐
But now you'll definitely know
whether or not you did it.
그건 알지만 이번에는
확실히 성사되는 거잖아
그래
I know.
And Chip promised that this time
it'd last at least for an entire song.
칩이 이번엔 최소한 노래
한 곡 끝날 때까지 버텨보겠대
I'm thinking of asking
Rachel out tonight...
오늘밤 레이첼이랑 외출해서
지난주에 쓴 곡 들려줄 거야
...maybe playing her that song
we wrote last week.
- 슬픔의 배낭?
- 그래
"Emotional Knapsack"?
Right on!
좋지
참! 너무 길게 하진 마
But don't take long.
We're testing our fake lD's tonight.
가짜 신분증 시험해야 하니까
그치, 클리포드 알바레즈?
Right, Clifford Alvarez?
Listen, Roland Cheng...
잘 들어, 롤랜드 쳉...
...if things go well,
I may be out with her all night.
일만 잘되면 밤새
레이첼하고 있을 거야
Dude, don't do that to me.
야, 이러지 마
It's cool, you can stay here.
My parents won't mind.
부모님은 괜찮으니까
우리 집에 있어
It's not that. I just don't want
to be stuck here with your fat sister.
네 꿀꿀이 여동생이랑
같이 있기 싫어서 그래
야
Why don't you finish off these pies?
이 파이 마저 먹어라
냉장고가 꽉 찼구나
I don't have any more room
in the fridge.
아뇨
No, thank you.
됐어요
Judy, you did it.
당신이 해냈어
She's finally full!
마침내 배가 불렀어
I called you fat?
내가 꿀꿀이라고 했어?
기억이 안 나는데
-I don't even remember that.
-Maybe it'd jog your memory...
'슬픔의 배낭'을 연주하면
생각이 날지도 모르지
...if you guys played
a little bit of "Emotional Knapsack."
I'm so sorry. I really am.
미안해, 진심이야
그때 난 바보였어
I was an idiot back then.
I rushed the stage at a Wham concert,
for crying out loud!
웸 콘서트에 가서
무대에 뛰어올라간 애야
세상에, 꿀꿀이라니
I can't believe you called her fat.
조지 마이클한테
따귀도 맞았대
I can't believe you let
George Michael slap you.
I am really sorry.
그런 말을 하다니
내가 죽일 놈이야
That is terrible. I'm so sorry.
That's not the Thanksgiving
I was talking about.
사실 그 추수감사절을
얘기한 게 아니었어
Yes, it was.
맞아, 그거야
No, it was actually
아니라니까, 그건...
자, 추수감사절 끝났다
누가 크리스마스트리 사올래
Thanksgiving's over.
Let's get ready for Christmas.
내가 재미있는
성탄절 얘기 알아
I have the cutest Christmas story.
모니카의 추수감사절
얘기부터 듣고
We want to hear Monica's story.
알았다, 허리가 부러진
난쟁이 얘긴데 할 수 없지 뭐
Mine had a dwarf that got broke in half,
but, you know, whatever.
- 1988년 추수감사절
- 레이첼, 엄마가 그러시는데
You changed your major again?
또 전공을 바꿨다면서?
I had to.
네, 심리학과 건물엔
주차장이 없어서요
There was never any parking
by the psychology building.
- 왔니, 레이첼?
- 안녕하세요
Love your new nose!
- 그 코 참 예쁘다
- 여보...
울프슨 박사는 예술가야
Dr. Wolfson's an artist.
내 사마귀도
잘라주셨다, 볼래?
He removed my mole cluster.
Want to see?
- 내가 나가죠
- 아뇨, 제가 열게요
No! Please, let me.
- 왔어?
- 안녕
행복한 추수감사절 맞으세요
Happy Thanksgiving.
헤어스타일이 확 바뀌었구먼
Your hair sure is different.
안 그래도 예전 모습이
너무 바보 같다던 참이죠
We were just talking about that.
We can't believe
how stupid we used to look.
- 모니카는요?
- 위층에 있다
Where's Monica?
She's upstairs.
모니카, 내려오너라
다들 왔구나
Come down, everyone's here!
Ross, Rachel...
로스, 레이첼,
추수감사절 싫어하는 애
...and the boy who hates Thanksgiving.
안녕, 챈들러
Oh, my God!
엄마야
What's the matter?
왜 그래...
내 드레스가 이상해?
Is there something on my dress?
You look so different.
완전히 딴판이네, 놀라워
Terrific.
That dress, that body....
드레스하며 몸매하며
- 야
- 미안
-Dude!
-Sorry.
그래, 모니카도
날씬해졌지만
Yes, she's thin. It's wonderful.
But we really want to hear...
우리 아들 여자친구
얘기부터 듣자꾸나
...about Ross' new girlfriend.
엄마도 참...
좋아요
Her name is Carol.
이름은 캐롤인데
정말 예쁘고 똑똑해요
She's really pretty and smart.
She's on the lacrosse team
and the golf team.
라크로스랑 골프를 해요
정말 놀랍죠?
Can you believe it?
She plays for both teams.
양쪽 팀에서 다 뛰어요
So I guess I'll see you at dinner.
챈들러, 저녁 먹을 때 봐
-Dude!
-Sorry.
- 이보게
- 죄송
Oh, my God!
세상에, 놀랄 일이다
That was so awesome.
You got him back
for calling you fat.
꿀꿀이라고 놀리더니
침 흘리는 것 좀 봐
He was drooling all over you.
-That must have felt so great.
-lt didn't.
너 속이 시원하겠다
- 그렇지 않아
- 아냐?
Yeah, I mean, I look great.
그래, 예쁘겠지
기분도 좋고 심장병도
없어지고, 기타 등등...
I feel great, and my heart's
not in trouble anymore.
I just don't feel
like I got him back.
그래도 찜찜해
I just want to humiliate him.
망신을 좀 당해야 돼
I want him to be naked, and
I want to point at him and laugh.
홀딱 벗겨놓고 비웃어주는 거야
좋아
That, we may be able to do.
그것도 가능하겠다
How?
어떻게?
남자들은 섹스하기 전에
홀랑 벗는 게 보통이지?
Guys tend to get naked
before they're going to have sex.
What?
뭐?
I didn't work this hard
and lose weight...
저런 애한테 내 꽃을 주려고
죽어라 살 뺀 줄 알아?
...just so I could give my flower
to someone like him.
First of all, if you keep calling it that,
no one will take it.
첫째, 그런 식으로 말하면
아무도 그 꽃 안 받아
And then second of all,
you're not going to have sex with him.
또...
둘째, 진짜로 하는 게 아니라
착각만 하게 만드는 거라고
You'll just make him
think that you are.
I'll throw him out
in the yard, lock the door...
홀랑 벗겨서 쫓아내면
동네 구경거리 되는 거지
...and all our neighbors
will just humiliate him!
그게 처절한 복수야
You'll definitely get him back.
그럼 어떻게
잠자리로 끌어들이지?
How do I make him think
I want to have sex?
Here's what you do.
이렇게 하자
Just act like everything around you
turns you on.
매순간 요염하게 나가는 거야
What do you mean?
어떻게?
뭐든 이용해
Anything can be sexy.
가령...
그렇지, 이 타월도 좋고
Like this dish towel.
This feels so good against my cheek.
뺨에 닿는 촉감이
너무 황홀해요
And if I get a little hot,
I can just dab myself with it.
땀이 나면 이렇게
살살 눌러주세요
Or I can bring it down to my side
and run it through my fingers...
말하는 중에 밑에서 손가락
사이로 살살 뽑아주시고요
...while I talk to him.
I can do that.
- 그 정도야 뭐
- 좋았어
Good, good, good.
Get busy. He's coming.
저기 온다
Hey, what's up?
- 왔어요?
- 네
그 멋진 마카로니치즈를
또 먹어볼 수 있을까?
Could you make me some of that
righteous mac and cheese like last year?
I'd love to.
그럼
우...
I love macaroni and cheese.
난 마카로니치즈 너무 좋아
I love the way this box feels
against my cheek.
이 박스 촉감이 진짜 황홀하네
알았어
난 당근도 좋아, 오...
And I love carrots.
Sometimes I like to put them
between my fingers.
가끔 손가락에 끼우고 싶어
Like this.
얘기하면서 이렇게
문질러주는 거야
And hold them down here
while I talk to you.
And, you know, if I get really hot...
이러다가 땀나잖아?
그럼 난...
...I like to pick up this knife.
칼을 들지
그리고...
차가운 금속의 감촉을..
And I put the cool steel...
...against...
어디냐...
...my body.
온몸으로 느껴
Are you all right?
너 괜찮니?
그럼, 괜찮지 않고
I'm fine.
상태는?
Twenty-year-old male.
20세 남자
우측 발가락 절단
He's got a severed toe
on his right foot.
Could you please not
do that feet first?
어떻게 발부터 들어옵니까?
발가락 잘렸다고
방금 말했잖아요
You know where his injury is.
Severed toe, you just said it!
It says the knife went
through your shoe.
식칼이 신발을 관통했다
당연하죠
고리버들 세공인데
They're made of wicker!
Did you bring the toe?
- 발가락 가져왔습니까?
- 네, 얼음에 재왔어요
I have it right here on ice.
얼음에 재서 싱싱합니다
매디슨스퀘어가든으로 오세요
Toes on Ice, coming soon
to Madison Square Garden.
Save your strength, man.
그냥 누워있어
곧 붙여드릴 테니까...
Don't worry, son.
We'll just reattach it and then....
뭐죠? 왜 그러세요?
What is it?
You brought a carrot.
당근 꼭다리네요
네?
발가락이 아니라
차가운 당근조각이에요
This isn't your toe. This is a small,
very cold piece of carrot.
You brought a carrot?
당근을 가져왔어?
Oh, my God!
맙소사, 우리 집 주방에
발가락이 굴러다닌다니
There's a toe in my kitchen.
이 일을 어쩌나
금방 가져올게요
I'm sorry! I'll go get it!
All we can do now
is sew up the wound.
너무 늦었어요
꿰매야 합니다
Without my toe? I need my toe!
내 발가락 내놔
I can go really fast!
Dad, give me the keys to your Porsche.
안 돼요
빨리 갔다 올게요
아빠 포르셰 키 주세요
그건 포기 못한다
I'm not falling for that one.
That's why I lost my toe?
Because I called you fat?
그래서 내 발가락이 없나?
꿀꿀이라고 한 것 때문에?
자를 생각은 없었어
실수였다고
I didn't mean to cut it off.
It was an accident.
덕분에 난 그동안
왕 절름발이로 통했어
That's why for an entire year
people called me Sir Limps-a-lot?
I'm sorry.
미안해
It wasn't your whole toe.
다 잘린 건 아니잖아
그 부분이 제일 좋았어
핵심이었다고
Yeah, well, I miss the tip.
It's the best part.
It has the nail.
발톱이 있었거든
챈들러
Sir Limps-a-lot.
그 별명 내가 지어준 거야
I came up with that.
독한 놈
You're a dork.
-I can't believe this.
-I said I was sorry.
- 믿을 수가 없군
- 미안하다고 했잖아
미안하다면 집 나간
새끼돼지가 돌아오나?
"Sorry" doesn't bring back the piggy
that cried all the way home.
우리가 이렇게 되다니
정말 후회가 막심하다
It figures that something like this
would happen today.
I hate this stupid day
and everything about it!
I'll see you later.
- 다음에 보자
- 잠깐, 챈들러
Wait.
Come here.
이리 와
내가 어떻게 해줄까?
뭐든...
Is there anything I can do?
Anything?
Just leave me alone for a little while.
잠깐 혼자 있고 싶어
I'm a duck.
I go quack-quack.
그래, 난 오리다
언제나 행복한 꽥꽥이
I'm happy all the time.
Nice try.
감동적이다
Wait, wait, wait.
이걸 봐
Look, Monica
- 저기, 모니카...
- 짜잔
This is not going to work.
소용없어
I bet this will work.
이건 어때?
참 보기 좋다
널 사랑해
You're so great.
I love you.
뭐?
Nothing. I said you're so great,
and then I just stopped talking.
아냐, 보기 좋다고만 하고
그냥 말 끊었어
You said you loved me.
I can't believe this!
지금 날 사랑한다고 했잖아
그런 적 없어
No, I didn't!
Yes, you did!
- 그랬다니까
- 아니라고
No, I didn't!
You love me!
- 날 사랑하는구나
- 절대 아냐
No, I don't!
그만! 그만! 그만! 그만!
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
1915년 추수감사절
Gauze!
거즈! 거즈!
거즈 좀 가져와요!
Gauze!
I need to get some gauze in here!
Can I please get some more gauze?
거즈가 더 필요해요!
This is getting ridiculous.
점점 웃기게 돌아가네
그래, 알았다